Anurag Saini's question is, he wants to know
what would be the easiest long-term answer for IC Lombard, which you would
hit straight six. The sector is like this, the company is like this,
you are thinking about the long term, no
problem.
Add one more thing, the results were also
good,
okay, no, this is a long-term sector, this is a
portfolio stock, there is a problem, but keep in
mind that you have talked about the long term,
then don't come back in two months.
I also remember that in the previous discussion you had
said that all the others, some healthcare
companies, some general companies, they have the entire
basket, so it means they benefit from it,
and it is not like that, see, sometimes having the entire
basket becomes useless if there is
unrelated diversification, or the entire
financial industry, so I think the
basket is fine,
but after
looking at the chart, where do
you feel that if someone wants to allocate, then a
good place for it,
its low is formed, that is,
1600, which should be formed, 1600 was a very efficient
place, so
how much can we take 16 down, it could be
16.  You can take it down to around
1550, even up to
1550, but 1550-1600 is becoming a very good zone for this.
If those with long term horizons
want to chip in here, then this is the right place.
I will not be able to stop the rest of the market-related fall
because even the good stocks that
I am watching are facing problems due to the market. Yes,
but still the story is that
if you look at the retracement, it
came around 50 to
61.8, from where you had a very good move
in February 2024, that level which is near 1500 will be formed,
around 15, it is coming to the same level at 61.8. There
could be a stretch case in this, Raj ji, but
this level at 62, I do not think it is
sustainable, although I will
not proceed on the assumption that why should we do sustainable
buying, then
do a cumulative analysis in the history of the chart that after the reversal, we should
enter it, then that is
not the way of investment.  The
more we get down, the better it is. Once
momentum is built, it's a different matter. However,
people ask this thing: let the trend come in,
then invest. I don't know, if it takes
24,000 points for it to come in, then I will lose 2,000 points. But
you
confused me. Earlier, I used to
follow this process that it has fallen, it is
near the comfort zone, it is near the support. Then
you used to say, no, turn around and confirm the
investment. Rajiv ji, I am
investing not for
trading, so I will always wait for the trend to be confirmed only then.
But as far as
investment is concerned, find out your valuation
level and until you do that,
I am asking about trading. By
default, my thinking goes towards investment. So,
if it goes towards investment,
then we will not do the chart for investment. For example,
see if we are at 22,000, we are
fully invested at 2,000, but the
trend is negative, so how should
we understand the valuation for investment?
Whatever we want to buy in a general
market and after that because I always
wrote this thing in my letter yesterday to
everyone that when we book profit or there is a
trending market then I
understand technical, when the market is
in Anandan correction then
you can keep yourself invested only on the basis of valuation
and you will have to allow yourself to be wrong for some time only then
you will make money because in technical you
bring a new analyst every new day a
new lower level will come and
one day or the other someone will be right and that is
also true.